Act like a villain, think like a hero.
Megamind vs. the Doom Syndicate is a animation, comedy,
science fiction film directed by Eric Fogel.
Megamind's former villain team, The Doom Syndicate, has returned.
Our newly crowned blue hero must now keep up evil appearances until he can assemble his friends (Roxanne,
Ol' Chum and Keiko) to stop his former evil teammates from launching Metro City to the Moon.
Megamind (voice), played by Keith Ferguson.
Roxanne Ritchi (voice), played by Laura Post.
OI' Chum (voice), played by Josh Brener.
Keiko Morita (voice), played by Maya Tuttle.
Lady Doppler (voice), played by Emily Tuñon.
Lord Nighty-Knight (voice), played by Talon Warburton.
Megamind vs.
the Doom Syndicate is a 2024 American animated direct-to-streaming superhero comedy film
produced by DreamWorks Animation Television and directed by Eric Fogel.
It is the sequel to the 2010 film, Megamind, in addition to serving as the pilot for
the television series, Megamind Rules!, which premiered the same day.
Starring Keith Ferguson, Laura Post, and Josh Brener, the film follows Megamind, now a superhero, as he
protects Metro City from his former allies in the Doom Syndicate, a team of supervillains.
Megamind vs.
the Doom Syndicate was released on Peacock on March 1, 2024, and
received generally negative reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of sequel,
aftercreditsstinger, low cost, low budget, absurd.
The tone is lighthearted and thought_provoking.